AKANBI ESTHER IBUKUNOLUWA

CONTACT

- @ ibukunakanbi6497@gmail.com
- **** +2348133660776. +2348157542685
- Halleluyah Way, Near Teak Forest, Agbaj e, Ijokodo, Ibadan
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/esther-ibuk unoluwa-akanbi-780b71169

SKILLS

Web development (Use of Basic HTML and CSS)

Inter-Communication

Strong Work Ethic

Vendor Management

Proficiency with Computer Application

Clientele Boosting

Customer Relation

Time Management

Handling Pressure

Confidentiality

Solving Problems

Digital Marketing

LANGUAGE

English

Yoruba

OBJECTIVE

A goal-driven individual with over 3 years of quality experience preparing reports, providing administrative and management services. I am looking to leverage my knowledge and experience to become a valuable asset in the corporate world.

EXPERIENCE

The Polytechnic Ibadan Health Centre, Ibadan

December 2018 - September 2019

Health Records Officer

- Contributed in the organization of the patient records of the institution clinic into a presentable database
- Analyzed and correctly filed each patient record referred to me in the clinic.
- Provided 100% correct and careful sorting of the patient records in order to ensure ease of access to the record when needed.
- During the creation of patient records, I painstakingly
 recorded every detail required by the clinic from each patient
 in their files.

Solar Clothings

2014 - 2017

Customer Service Representative

- Oversaw the efficient running of a stall working 20 hours a
 week while studying
- ☑ Ensured a 100% detailing of the income and expenditure of the stall.
- Provided a daily report and account of sales and events surrounding these sales.
- Provided customer support service while simultaneously ensuring sales.

National Population Commission

2014 - 2014

- Distributed hundreds of birth certificates among the residents
 of the Ibadan North East local government.
- Conducted numerous house-to-house delivery of birth
 certificates among the locals

EDUCATION

University of Ibadan

2018

B.Sc Physiology

Santa Clara University

2020

Starting a Business 2019 course

Google

2019

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing



CENFEX High School 2013 SSCE